When your family is closing you in, music may be the only way out.
Light of Day is a music, drama film directed by Paul Schrader.
Cleveland siblings rise with a rock band while coping with personal problems.
Joe Rasnick, played by Michael J. Fox.
Janette Rasnick, played by Gena Rowlands.
Patti Rasnick, played by Joan Jett.
Bu Montgomery, played by Michael McKean.
Smittie, played by Thomas G. Waites.
Cindy Montgomery, played by Cherry Jones.
Light of Day is a 1987 American musical drama film starring Michael J.
Fox, Gena Rowlands and Joan Jett in her film debut.
It was written and directed by Paul Schrader.
The original music score was composed by Thomas Newman
and the cinematography is by John Bailey.
The film explores themes of rock 'n' roll, sibling relationship,
parent child relationship, cleveland, musical.
The tone is emotional.